http://www.heel.com/en/privacy-policy.html

Contact
About HeelCompany PortraitFacts and FiguresDELTONManufacturingHistoryDirectionsProductsHuman MedicineVeterinary MedicineResearchPreclinical ResearchClinical ResearchHans-Heinrich Reckeweg Clinical Case AwardScientific NetworkNEURIM: A Study on NeurexanTherapeutic ApproachHelping patients live healthier lives
Home
Heel Worldwide
Careers
Careers at Heel
Heel as an Employer
Vacancies
Awards
Contact
Data Privacy Policy
We are pleased that you are visiting our website. We take the protection of your personal data very seriously.Please find information below according to Articles 13 and 14 of the GDPR on processing your personal data which we are pleased to provide in this data privacy policy.
1. Processing of personal data when using our website. 1.1 Accessing the website (1) For purely informative use of our website, i.e. if you do not register or transfer information to us by other means, we only collect the personal data that your browser transfers to our server. In this regard, we collect the following information that is technically necessary for us to display our website and to ensure its stability and safety: IP address of the requesting processorDate and time of the requestName and URL of the file retrievedInformation on the operating system and its status of access/HTTP status codeVolume of data transmittedWebsite from which our site was accessed Browser and language and version of the browser software (2) The legal basis for processing is the balancing of interests according to Art. 6 Para. 1 (1) Letter f of the GDPR.
The data specified are processed by us for the following purposes:
To ensure trouble-free connection to the websiteEvaluation of system safety and stabilityAnalysis of unauthorised access or attempts to access the system (3) The listed data are automatically deleted after a period of one month.
1.2 Using our contact formDescription of the data processing(1) If you have any questions, you can contact us using a form provided on our website. To do so, you need provide a valid email address as well as other data for the required fields so that we know who sent the request and which enables us to answer this. Other information can be entered voluntarily.Legal basis and purpose of the data processing(2) The legal basis for processing is the balancing of interests according to Art. 6 Para. 1 (1) Letter f of the GDPR.We process the data listed for the following purposes: Getting in touchResponding to specific questions Retention period(3) Subject to statutory retention periods, the personal data are erased after a period of 90 days after the question has been answered, to enable a response to further queries. 1.3 Google MapsDescription of the data processing (1) On our website we are using the component "Google Maps" of the company Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 USA, subsequently „Google“,.With every usage of the component "Google Maps" a cookie is placed, to process user settings and user data on the page, where the component "Google Maps" is integrated. This cookie is usually not deleted when closing the browser, but runs out after a certain amount of time, as long as it is not deleted by you manually.If you do not agree to the processing of your data, it is possible to deactivate the service "Google Maps" and thereby preventing the transmission of data to Google. For this, please deactivate the java script function in your browser. However, in this case you cannot use "Google Maps" or you can use it only with limited functionality.The usage of "Google Maps" and the information received via "Google Maps" is done according to the Google usage policies http://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/terms/regional.html as well as the additional terms and conditions of „Google Maps“ https://www.google.com/intl/de_de/help/terms_maps.html. 1.4 Using Adobe FontsOur website uses so-called web fonts, which are provided by Adobe, for the uniform representation of fonts.Provider is Adobe Systems Incorporated, 345 Park Avenue, San Jose, CA 95110-2704, USA (Adobe).When you call up a page, your browser loads the required web fonts into your browser cache to correctly display texts and fonts. To do this, the browser you are using must connect to the Adobe servers.This will give Adobe notice that our website has been accessed via your IP address. The use of Adobe Fonts is in the interest of a uniform and attractive presentation of our online services.This constitutes a legitimate interest within the meaning of Art. 6 para. 1 lit. f GDPR.If your browser does not support web fonts, a default font will be used by your computer.For more information about Adobe Fonts, visit https://fonts.adobe.com/ and the Adobe privacy policy at https://www.adobe.com/privacy/policies/adobe-fonts.html.
2. Notes on consent for provision of the personal data
(1) If you have given consent for processing of your data, you may withdraw this at any time. Such a withdrawal of consent affects the admissibility of processing your personal data based on the consent you gave before its withdrawal.
When withdrawing your consent, we kindly ask you to use one of the contact options listed in the disclaimer. (2) The provision of personal data is not a statutory or contractual requirement, or a requirement necessary to enter into a contract.
3. Recipients of personal data(1) Within the EU/EEC:All website data are stored on servers within the EU/EEC Member States.(2) Outside of the EU/EEC – third countries:Transfer to a third country (outside of the EU/EEC) does not take place.
4. Use of cookies We use cookies to make our website attractive and user-friendly, to optimise it and to process requests more quickly.
These are small text files that are saved on your computer and which store certain settings and data for exchange with our system via your browser. Cookies do not damage your computer and do not contain any malware such as viruses.
We use cookies that are necessary for operating the website. These ensure functions without which the website cannot be used as intended. These are session cookies that are only saved on your computer for the duration of your visit to our website. (2) The legal basis for processing is the balancing of interests according to Art. 6 Para. 1 (1) Letter f of the GDPR.5. Notes on reporting side effectsIf you suspect side effects or a lack of drug effect, medication errors, misuse or off-label use or other aspects relating to the safety of a Heel product, please contact your physician, pharmacist or naturopath, the local health authority or contact Heel directly.If you inform us about unwanted side effects or other aspects relating to the safety of one of our Heel products, we are obliged by law to process your report. This may also make it necessary for us to contact you to clarify questions. We may then have to report the information that you have given us to the responsible health authorities: in this case, your information will be forwarded only in pseudonymous form so that no information is forwarded that identifies you directly.We also may have to forward these pseudonymous reports to our subsidiaries and partners insofar as they in turn are obliged to make reports to the health authorities responsible for them. For more information about privacy and reporting side effects, please refer to the Heel Privacy policy for pharmacovigilance data. 6. Your rights (1) You have the following rights in regard to your personal data: Art. 15 of the GDPR Right of accessRight of access to your personal data that is stored by us.Art. 16 of the GDPR Right to rectification Right to rectification of your personal data that is inaccurate.Art. 17 of the GDPR Right to erasure Erasure of your personal data provided that no statutory retention periods exist.Art. 18 of the GDPR Right to restriction of processingIf certain conditions are met, you have the right to restriction of processing of your personal data and these will not be processed further.Art. 20 GDPR Right to data portabilityRight to data portability of your personal data that you provided to us.Art. 21 of the GDPR Right to object to processing
(2) You also have the right to lodge a complaint with a data protection Supervisory Authority. (3) There is no automated decision-making including profiling according to Article 22 Para. 1 and 4.7. External linksOur website contains links to third party websites that are specially designated and whose content is not located on our server. The external contents of these links was checked when the links were set up. However, it cannot be ruled out that the contents were subsequently amended by the respective providers. If you should notice that the content of external providers infringes any applicable laws, then please advise us. This data privacy policy only applies to the content on our servers.
8. Contact details (1) The name and contact details of the controller and their representative: Biologische Heilmittel Heel GmbHDr.-Reckeweg-Str. 2 - 476532 Baden-BadenEmail: info@heel.de You can find more information in the disclaimer. (2) Contact details of the Data Protection Officer:Biologische Heilmittel Heel GmbHData Protection OfficerDr.-Reckeweg-Str. 2 - 476532 Baden-BadenEmail: dataprotection@heel.com 9. Amendments to this data privacy policy We will revise this data privacy policy from time to time to adapt it to the state-of-the-art or to revised legal frameworks.
Therefore, we recommend that you regularly inform yourself about changes to this webpage.
Dated: May 2018
Use of cookies: We would like to use cookies in order to understand the preferences of our visitors, and to be able to design this website optimally. For detailed information, including on how you can revoke your consent at any time, please see our Privacy Policy.
Show more
Show less
I agree
Decline
About Heel
Heel Worldwide
Careers
Directions
